{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","address":"150 W Congress","zipcode":"48226","owner":"George Sboukis","licenseNumber":"217955","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/19/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E61000003864C0150DC354C0482BFE29342A4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"42021","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","inspectionDate":"2018-04-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"2","pfcount":"1","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42021","inspectionDate":"4/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"42021","inspectionDate":"4/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-04-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"42021","inspectionDate":"4/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"3-501.13","violationDescription":"POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be thawed:  Under refrigeration, or under cool running water (<70° F), or as part of cooking process, and total accumulated time above 41° F, for thawed portions, shall not exceed 4 hours.  Any thawing procedure may be used for immediate service for individual consumers order of READY-TO-EAT foods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Frozen food(s) for thawing","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored in water","subProblem":"That is standing","location":"PREP SINK","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-04-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Use cool, running water with enough flow to remove particles."},{"inspectionid":"42021","inspectionDate":"4/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Raw ready-to-eat food(s)","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-04-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."}]},{"inspectionid":"40121","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","inspectionDate":"2017-09-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"2","pfcount":"3","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"5","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"5","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40121","inspectionDate":"9/28/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"Not covered","location":"ICE BIN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store in a protective manner."},{"inspectionid":"40121","inspectionDate":"9/28/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"40121","inspectionDate":"9/28/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Equipment/utensils","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate separation to prevent contamination."},{"inspectionid":"40121","inspectionDate":"9/28/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Equipment slicer","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"SLICER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"40121","inspectionDate":"9/28/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"40121","inspectionDate":"9/28/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"6-302.11","violationDescription":"A supply of toilet tissue shall be available at each toilet.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Toilet paper","subItem":"at toilet in restroom employee","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"38462","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","inspectionDate":"2017-03-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","inspectorid":"122","pcount":"1","pfcount":"1","ccount":"6","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"6","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38462","inspectionDate":"3/11/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"fasteners","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"Walk-in cooler & Walk-in freezer","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"inspectionid":"38462","inspectionDate":"3/11/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"38462","inspectionDate":"3/11/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"5-204.11","violationDescription":"A HANDWASHING SINK shall be located: \r\n(A) To allow convenient use by EMPLOYEES in FOOD preparation, FOOD dispensing, and WAREWASHING areas;  (Pf)and\r\n(B) In, or immediately adjacent to, toilet rooms. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"In dishwash area","location":"WARE WASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hand sink in same room as dish handling."},{"inspectionid":"38462","inspectionDate":"3/11/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"4-202.16","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall be free of unnecessary ledges, projections, and crevices, and designed and constructed to allow easy cleaning and to facilitate maintenance.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"WARE WASHING AREA","subLocation":"Ice machine","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."},{"inspectionid":"38462","inspectionDate":"3/11/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than","subProblem":"10 foot candles","location":"COFFEE STATION/ BAR","subLocation":"Lights","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"38462","inspectionDate":"3/11/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than","subProblem":"20 foot candles","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"38462","inspectionDate":"3/11/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"4-202.16","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall be free of unnecessary ledges, projections, and crevices, and designed and constructed to allow easy cleaning and to facilitate maintenance.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With ledges, projections, or crevices","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."},{"inspectionid":"38462","inspectionDate":"3/11/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5194","name":"The Caucus Club","violationCode":"3-306.11","violationDescription":"Except for nuts in the shell and whole, raw fruits and vegetables that are intended for hulling, peeling, or washing by the CONSUMER before consumption, FOOD on display shall be protected from contamination by the use of PACKAGING; counter, service line, or salad bar FOOD guards; display cases; or other effective means. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food on display","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Lacking protection","subProblem":"Other effective means","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Ice bin","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Protect against contamination"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5194"}}